goodcook.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last updated: July 1, 2009   
Good Cook, the leading brand of kitchenware in America has created, GoodCook.com as a service to you. The mission of our site is to provide you with an informative and fun environment, where you can learn and share your thoughts about food; how to shop for it, prepare it, serve it and enjoy it. In doing so we are committed to respecting your privacy. This policy statement outlines our use of personal information collected through GoodCook.com. It is incorporated into and is subject to the Good Cook Terms of Use, which can be accessed atÂ  term of use . Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide on the Website is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and Good Cookâ€™s Terms of Use. 

This Privacy Policy, along with the Terms of Use is posted on our Website. You should review it frequently, as it may change from time to time without notice. When you access GoodCook.com you will have the opportunity to agree to this policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, or its changes we may subsequently make, you have the opportunity to stop accessing the Website immediately. 

A. COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  

## 1\. Collection of personal information

You will have the opportunity to browse parts of our Website without telling us who you are or without revealing any personal information about yourself. If you want to become a full fledged member of the community with an online account, make purchases, provide pictures of yourself, submit recipes or videos, provide cooking tips, shopping hints or comments; participate in contests, polls or request information on products, services or content you will need to agree to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. 

Many of these above activities require you to provide personal information about yourself. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name; contact information, credit card information and billing address; email; username; password; and certain demographic information such as age or date of birth, your favorite stores where you purchase food, the size of your family, and other information relevant to user surveys and/or special offers. We may also collect personal information that you provide in the material you post to our Website or in your correspondence with us.

We may supplement the information you provide to us with data we receive from third parties, such as marketing firms or address verification services. For example if you change your address and fail to advise us we may verify with a third party address verification company. 

## 2\. User Content

You or anyone using our Website is defined as a â€œuserâ€�. â€œUser Contentâ€� is any material posted by you to our Website.

Any User Content, such as images, videos, recipes, comments posted by you to our Website becomes published content and is provided on a non-proprietary and non-confidential basis. It will be accessible by other Users on this Website and can be used by those people to identify you and/or send you unsolicited communications. Please be sure that any information you provide on any area of our Website is information you are comfortable sharing with others. 

## 3\. Collection of Aggregate and Anonymous Information

In the process of providing us with your personal information and in your enjoyment of our website we may collect and aggregate anonymous information such as your browser type, your ISP or operating system, the URL of previous websites you visited, and your IP address. We may share this information, which does not personally identify you, with our marketing partners, affiliates or agents for various administrative and marketing purposes.   

## 4\. Cookies

We may collect information from you by using cookies. A cookie is a small text file stored on your computer containing information about you. Cookies help us analyze Web traffic, provide user data for a particular webpage, and allow Web applications to be responsive to you as an individual. This helps us tailor our operations to your specific needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. If you would prefer to prevent your computer from accepting our cookies, please follow your Internet browserâ€™s steps for doing so. However, if you do disable cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of all our online features or access certain sections of our Website. 

B. USES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  

## 1\. How Personal Information is Used

We may use your personal information for any of the following reasons:  
Create an online account for you on our Website;Â   
Verify your identity when you sue certain areas or features of our Website;Â   
Internal record keeping;Â   
To complete your online order and send you he products you purchased;Â   
To share with third party service providers who may provide services to you or perform other services on our behalf (e.g. to process payments, or ship products you have ordered);Â   
To improve our Websiteâ€™s content and for general administration;Â   
To provide customer support;Â   
To more carefully direct our Website content and online offers to you preferences;Â   
To periodically send promotional information regarding new products or special offers, contests, or other information we think you might find of interest from our company, our affiliates, and our marketing partners;Â   
To contact you, via email, telephone, facsimile or mail to deliver certain information you have requested;Â   
To more effectively advise you ofÂ  product, promotional and contest opportunities that might be attractive to you based on the demographic information you have provided us ( i.e., age, postal code, address, shopping habits, and other various data).Â    

## 2\. Other Disclosures of Personal Information

There are potentially business and/or legal reasons we may be required to disclose your personal information. 

As an example in a business transition your personal information may be one of the assets that would be affected. We may transfer information we have about you to third parties in connection with a merger, sale or acquisition involving all or part of our company, or as part of a corporate reorganization or stack sale or other change in corporate control.

We may also be required by law to provide your personal information to law enforcement or a government agency in response to a search warrant, subpoena or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body. We may also disclose your personal information where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, to protect our interest or preserve our rights, or as otherwise permitted or required by law. 

C. POLLS AND SURVEYS  
In the spirit of open communication on our Website we will offer you opportunities to provide feedback, input, and comments. While your participation in these activities is completely voluntary some of them may require you to provide additional personal information, as detailed below.   

## 1\. Polling

We may invite you to participate in polls so you can easily share your opinions with others and see what our audience thinks about certain topics. Your opinion or responses are collected in the aggregate and do not identify individual Users. We may use a system to â€œtagâ€� Users after they have voted so we can ensure that Users vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with your personal information.   

## 2\. Surveys

In order to constantly improve our products, the Website and our promotional offerings we may from time to time conduct surveys. As part of the process, we may share your individual responses from these surveys with our affiliates and /or third party marketing partners, who may, in turn use this information to send you special offers or promotional material.   

## 3\. Contests

One of the most exciting offerings on the Website will be an ongoing series of contests, which will allow you to compete with other Users for prizes. There will be contests built around recipes, videos, participation on the Website, or contribution of specific content.

Contest entry rules or procedures will be specific to each contest and spelled out in detail at the time the contest is offered. If you decide to participate you will be required to comply with the rules of the specific contest.

Your content submitted in a given contest on our Website may be displayed publicly online, on our packaging of one or more of our products, in advertisements, in printed or electronic media, or posted on any other medium we select at our sole discretion. By entering one of our contests you agree to the use of your User Content in this manner, including but not limited to any personal information we choose to include with it. 

D. CHILDRENS PRIVACY  
Our Website is not intended for anyone under the age of 13. As addressed in the federal Childrenâ€™s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and associated rules, we do not knowingly collect or maintain any personal information from anyone under the age of 13. 

At the same time, GoodCook.com is a food focused Website that is central to families. Good Cook encourages the family to participate on the Website individually or together. If children do participate it is important they participate under adult supervision. If you are a parent or guardian and believe your child has provided personal information on our Website, please contactÂ Â  (link) so we can delete the childâ€™s information. 

E. SECURITY  
We use procedural and technological security measures which are reasonably designed to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure, consistent with industry standards. 

We use encryption, passwords, and physical security measures to help protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, it is always possible that third parties will unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or defeat these measures. Therefore, we do not promise and cannot guarantee (and thus you should not expect) that your personal information can never be viewed and/or used by others. Good Cook is not responsible for these unauthorized uses, thus you should be careful about the information you post or otherwise make available when using our Website. 

F. LINKS TO EXTERNAL WEBSITES  
Our Website may contain links to other sites that we do not own or operate. Also links to our Website may be featured on third party websites on which we advertise.

We provide links to third party Websites as a convenience to you. These links are not intended as an endorsement of or referral to the linked Websites. We recommend you carefully read the privacy statements, notices and Terms of Use of any other websites that you visit. We do not have any control over such Websites, and therefore we assume no responsibility or liability for the manner in which the organizations that operate such linked Websites collect, use or disclose, secure or otherwise treat your personal information. 

G. RESTRICTING, DELETING AND CORRECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

1\. You can review, correct and delete your personal information and personal preferences by logging into the Website and navigating to your preferences page in â€œMy Profileâ€�

2\. You may opt-out of receiving commercial emails from us by clicking on the â€œunsubscribeâ€� link in every commercial emails we send.

3\. You may contact us by phone at 1. 800 (new number) or by mail at the following address and request that your personal information be updated, corrected or deleted: 

Good Cook Website  
9409 Buffalo Avenue  
Rancho Cucamonga, CA 91730  
Attention: Web Marketing Administrator 

Upon receiving your request we will make the changes or deletions you request as soon as reasonably possible. You should understand, however, that once you publicly post User Content or any other information onto the Website, you may not be able to change or remove it. 

H. ACCOUNT PROTECTION  
Your password is the key to your account. When creating your password, you should use unique numbers, letters, special characters, and combinations thereof. In addition, DO NOT disclose your password to anyone. If you do share our password or your personal information with others, you are solely responsible for all actions taken with respect to your online account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control of your personal information and be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Thus, IF YOUR PASSWORD HAS BEEN COMPROMISED FOR ANY REASON, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY NOTIFY GOODCOOK TO CHANGE YOUR PASSWORD.   
I.UPDATES TO THIS POLICY  
This Privacy Policy is current as of the effective date set forth above. Please consult this portion of the Website periodically as Good Cook may at any time revise this Privacy Policy by updating this webpage. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the current version of this Privacy Policy. If at any time you choose not to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should not use this Website. 

If we make a material (meaning major or significant) change to this Privacy Policy that affects personal information we collected from you prior to the date of the material change, we will give you the opportunity to decide whether we may use your personal information in this manner. 

J. INTERNATIONAL VISITORS TO THIS SITE  
Our computer systems are currently based in the United States, so your personal information will be processed by us in the United States, where data protection and privacy regulations may be different than other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create an online account on this Website as a visitor from outside the United States, you will have agreed to terms of Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use and you will have consented the transfer to and processing of all such information I the United States, which may not offer and equivalent level of protection of that in the European Union or certain other countries.   
K. QUESTIONS, COMMENTS, OR OTHER FEEDBACK  
We want to hear from you and encourage you to contact us if you have any questions, comments or other feedback about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
